Guide to the Edwin "Bud" Shrake Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Fiction, 1959-2006
  - The Borderland, 1976-2008, undated
    - Research
      - Frontier Times (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, notes (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Clippings (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Corrected manuscript and typescript fragments (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, bibliography, articles (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files
      - Austin (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Caldwell (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Captured by Indians (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Council House and Plum Creek (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Dora (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Dr. Swift (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Environment (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - General Background (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Hannah (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Indians (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - People on battles and their own accounts (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Rangers (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - San Antonio (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Sketches of Texas (mimeo) (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Various (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Notebook (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Notes to Self" (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Chapter notes (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous manuscript and typescript notes (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Typescript fragments with notes attached (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Corrected typescript fragments (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Chapter notes and corrected typescript fragments (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Chapter notes and corrected typescript fragments (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy, part 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Draft fragments (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Annotated and corrected draft printout, part 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Annotated draft printout, part 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/synopses/draft samples, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Annotated correspondence/synopsis/draft sample (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Draft cover layout (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - "Bill's Copy 5/8/97" draft printout, page 1-158, May 8, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Corrected draft printout, page 1-288 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Corrected draft printout with notes, page 1-387 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Printout copy fragment, page 240-359 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Corrected draft printout, with correspondence (first draft) (Box 19, Folder 4-5, Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts (Box 20, Folder 3-6)
    - Corrected draft printout fragments (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, page 1-212 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, page 396-end (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, page 363-end (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Annotated draft printout with edit notes (first revision) (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
    - Notebooks (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, part (second revision) (Box 22, Folder 6, Box 23, Folder 1-3)
    - Draft printout (second revision) (Box 23, Folder 4-7)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, part 5 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Annotated printout, part 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Corrected draft printout with inserts, p. 11-246 (Haber revision) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Hyperion contract (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Corrected and annotated fragments (first Haber revision) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Draft printout, with correspondence (Haber revision) (Box 24, Folder 6-7, Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Corrected copy edit printout, part 1 (Box 25, Folder 3-6)
    - Electronic draft files on two diskettes/one CD-R (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Corrected page proofs (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Cover renderings (Box 151)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2008, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Research for Volume 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Reviews (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Promotion (Box 26, Folder 8, Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Billy Boy, 2000-2009
    - Notes (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Corrected and annotated draft printout (first draft) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Draft printout (first draft corrected) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Corrected and annotated draft printout with inserts (second draft) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Draft printout (second draft corrected) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Promotion (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Custer's Brother's Horse, 2002-2008, undated
    - Research (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    - Notes (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Draft printout photocopy (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and promotion (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Unpublished Short Stories and Fragments, circa 1950-1979
    - Blue Lem If It Rains (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - The Bugles of the Cherubim (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Carbon Copy (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Eddie (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Fly Away, Lulu (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - The Intrasitive Obligory (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - The Last Recital (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - The Man Who Had Been Crucified (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Revenge (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Untitled (Billy Twist) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Untitled (Curly) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Untitled (Frank & Billy) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Untitled (Max Ormand) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Untitled (Red McGill) (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Untitled (Seth Hawkins) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Untitled (Lions golf club) (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Various notes and fragments (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Unfinished Novels, 1965-2009, undated
    - These Happy Occasions – synopsis, correspondence, corrected typescript (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Carl's Bad Tavern
      - Corrected partial draft printout with notes and clippings (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Corrected draft printout (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - The Crazy Water Golf Club – notes, draft fragments, research (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - The Monster on the Mountain – correspondence (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Malibu Zulu, 2008, undated
      - Notes and research (including other projects) (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Corrected printout with inserts (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Draft printout (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Corrected draft printout fragments (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Screenplays/Teleplays, 1971-2002, undated
  This series is also divided into Produced and Unproduced work.
  The Produced sub-series is arranged by production date. It contains similar materials: drafts, correspondence, contracts, promotional materials and press clippings. The three projects Shrake was most closely involved with — Kid Blue, Songwriter and Pair of Aces — contain the most materials. The Beverly Hills Cop II folders contain documents related to the unsuccessful arbitration Shrake and Dan Jenkins initiated in order to get writing credits on the movie.
  The Unproduced sub-series is the most voluminous, reflecting Shrake's prolific work as a screenwriter from the early 1970s to the early 1990s. Except for the three film treatments at the beginning, the files are arranged alphabetically. Contents are typically drafts and treatments, with some correspondence and research. Those works that contain more materials than others often reflect that they were closer to being produced, such as with "The Big Mamoo," the various Pancho Villa projects,and "Slim and None." Shrake collaborated with Dan Jenkins in the 1970s and 80s on many of the unproduced screenplay efforts. Two of Shrake's attempts to turn his novels into films are also contained here: Strange Peaches and Limo, the latter written with Jenkins.
  - J.W. Coop, 1971-1972, undated
    - "Rodeo" corrected draft typescript photocopy with fragments (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - "Rodeo" draft typescript photocopy (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and lawsuit (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and promotion (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Kid Blue, 1971-1998, undated
    - Notes (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript photocopy (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript photocopy (final draft) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Annotated final shooting script (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Corrected final shooting script (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Corrected final shooting script photocopy (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Shooting schedule (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
    - General filed materials (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Publicity (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Nightwing, 1977-1979, undated
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Lending Agreements (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Annotated and corrected draft typescript (first draft) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Annotated and corrected draft typescript photocopy (first draft) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy (first draft) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy (second draft) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Corrected composite draft typescript/photocopy (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Press and promotion (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Tom Horn, 1978-1979
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Annotated draft typescript notes with Steve McQueen notes (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Promotion and publicity (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Final shooting script (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Songwriter, 1978-1985, undated
    - Final shooting script (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript notes (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Treatment typescript (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Early corrected draft typescript (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript photocopy with notes, September 1, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Corrected typescript photocopy fragment, January 1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Three original typescripts with notes to Jane, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy, 118 pages, January 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy, 115 pages, January 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Corrected, incomplete draft typescript photocopy, January 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy, 115 pages, January 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy, 115 pages, January 1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy, 117 pages, June 1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Corrected draft typescript with notes, 98 pages, August 1, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy, 113 pages, August 15, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript photocopy, 114 pages, August 23, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Corrected draft typescript copy of final script, 104 pages, September 12, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Draft typescript copy of final script, 104 pages, September - October 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript, 121 pages, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Corrected typescript photocopy fragments with manuscript letter (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Draft typescript and photocopy fragments, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript photocopy, 117 pages, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy with inserts, 118 pages, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Draft typescript photocopy, 118 pages, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Draft typescript and photocopy, 99 pages, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Production (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Press, 1978-1983 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Press, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Press, 1985, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Publicity (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - General (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Beverly Hills Cop II, 1985-1989, undated
    - Notecards (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Original treatment with correspondence (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Corrected typescript photocopy fragment with memo (first draft) (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Draft typescript photocopy (first draft) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Draft typescript photocopy (revised first draft) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Annotated draft typescript photocopy (second draft) (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Draft typescript [second draft] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Annotated photocopy of first shooting script (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Photocopy of second shooting script (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Arbitration, 1985-1990
      - Notes and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Notes and correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Notes and correspondence, 1988-1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Court documents (Box 40, Folder 6, Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Pair of Aces (a.k.a. "RIP"), circa 1969-1991
    - Notes and research (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Fragment copy and corrected typescript copy ("older version") (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Corrected draft typescript photocopy with inserts, June 12, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Incomplete typescript photocopy, June 12, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Typescript carbon copy, June 12, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Typescript photocopy, June 12, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Corrected typescript photocopy with inserts, circa August 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Signed typescript photocopy, circa August 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Typescript photocopy, August 9, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Typescript photocopy, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Typescript (third draft), June 15, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Inscribed printout, July 20, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Incomplete, annotated photocopy, circa July 1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Call Sheets and Daily Production Reports, October 23 - November 13, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Shooting Script, October 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Final Shooting Script, November 1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - General production documents (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Production binder (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and clippings (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Framed press photo (Box 151)
  - Screenplays/Teleplays – Unproduced, 1973-2001, undated
    - Three [film] treatments (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Beyond - printout photocopy, January 7, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - The Big Mamoo, 1978-1986, undated
      - Notes (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Research: "Some Men and Moments in the History of Nuclear Physics" (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Research: "The Secret History of the Atomic Bomb" (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Research: City of Fire (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Research: Clippings (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Corrected typescript (first draft), October 1980 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Typescript (first draft), October 1980 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Typescript with inserts (first draft), October 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Typescript (draft #2), December 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy with inserts, December 1980-February 1981 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Typescript, January 14, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Typescript, February 15, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Inscribed typescript, February 15, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Typescript, November 1981 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Incomplete typescript, January 1982 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy, January 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Inscribed and corrected typescript photocopy, February 1986 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Typescript, March 1986 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Corrected composite manuscript fragments with note (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Bino's Blues, 1994-1996, undated
      - Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Corrected fragments, notes, original draft (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Three corrected draft printouts (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - The Cowboy and the Cat – notes, correspondence, drafts (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - The Cowboy Detective (a.k.a. Cowboy Dick), 1992-1993, undated
      - Correspondence, agreements (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Research, notes, drafts (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Damn Yankees, 1983-1984, undated
      - Notes, clippings, correspondence (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Scenarios (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Corrected transcript photocopy with notes, correspondence (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - First Draft printout, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - First Draft printout, July 1983 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Corrected First Draft photocopy with note, August 22, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Corrected First Draft photocopy with inserts, November 1, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Revised First Draft photocopy with note, November 1, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Corrected First Draft photocopy, November 9, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Revised First Draft photocopy, November 9, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Inscribed First Draft photocopy, January 1, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Corrected photocopy fragments (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Dinosaur Wine, 1980-1981, undated
      - Typescript photocopy (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, notes, correspondence (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Fargo Shagrew, 1984, undated
      - Notes, correspondence, incomplete draft with notes (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Draft typescript and photocopy with inserts (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - First Among the Best, 1984-2002, undated
      - Research and notes (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - File cards (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - First Draft printout, March 1, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Draft printout, March 28, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Incomplete, corrected draft printout, March 28, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Draft photocopy/printout, April 9, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Draft printout, May 15, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Draft printout, May 21, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Corrected draft photocopy, June 10, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Draft printout, June 18, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Draft printout and signed photocopy, November 1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Draft photocopy, April 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Draft printout, June 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Corrected draft printout, July 5, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Draft printout, July 5, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Printout fragments (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Draft printout, June 7, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Girlcop, 1992, undated
      - Correspondence, treatment, notes, research (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - The Great McGinty, 1980, undated
      - Handwritten notes (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Corrected "1st draft" typescript, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, February 18, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Typescript photocopy with note, March 31, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Typescript photocopy, November 1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Hanging Sunday, undated
      - Corrected typescript, incomplete (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - The Killer Sigh, June 1983
      - Typescript photocopy (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Annotated/corrected/inscribed typescript photocopy (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - King Jack (a.k.a. The Coral Island), 1982-2001, undated
      - Notes, correspondence, research (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Photocopy of The Coral Island by R.M. Ballantyne, with notes (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Typescript fragments (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Three original typescripts, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy with insert, incomplete, September 1983 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Notes, research, corrected typescript with inserts, November 1983 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Draft typescript, March 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy, March 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Typescript photocopy, June 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Typescript photocopy with e-mail and note, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Limo, 1975-1983
      - Annotated transcript photocopy, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, notes, research, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript, January 6, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, circa April 1977 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Corrected and inscribed typescript photocopy, April 21, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, April 21, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Paramount Memorandum of Agreement, May 23, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Loose Women, 1983-1984
      - Correspondence, notes, treatment (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Incomplete typescript photocopy, November 1, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Inscribed typescript copy (first draft), November 2, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Typescript photocopy with notes and inserts, February 1984 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - ncomplete, corrected typescript photocopy, February 1984 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Typescript photocopy, February 1984 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Lost Tampico Mine, undated
      - Incomplete typescript copy, fragments, notes (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - The Mandarin Silo, April 1982, undated
      - Notes, correspondence, drafts (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Murder Clear, 1986-1993, undated
      - Notes, correspondence, research (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Incomplete, corrected typescript with inserts (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Typescript (first draft), undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Typescript (rough draft), April 15, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Inscribed, corrected typescript photocopy (rough draft), April 15, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Inscribed, corrected typescript with insert (second rough draft) (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy (second rough draft), May 1, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Corrected typescript with inserts, September 1986 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Draft typescript, September 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Annotated typescript with insert, January 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy with clipping, January 1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Draft typescript (second draft), August 1988 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Draft printout, February 1996 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Myrabelle Shirley: A Love Story (a.k.a. Belle Starr), 1979-1991, undated
      - Correspondence, notes, research (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy with inserts, May 4, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy, May 4, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy, May 4, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Draft typescript, circa August 1, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Inscribed typescript photocopy, August 1, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Corrected typescript with notes, circa March 21, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Typescript photocopy, October 1989 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Typescript photocopy with note, May 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Corrected typescript fragments, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Ned Blessing, July 1, 1991
      - Draft typescript and photocopy (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans, Land of Dreams or, The Louisiana Silo, 1992, undated
      - Corrected, incomplete typescript (first draft) (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Draft typescript (first draft) (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Corrected typescript photocopy (first draft) (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, fragments, notes (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Corrected typescript (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - The Night of the Knife, undated
      - Two corrected typescripts (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Pancho Villa Projects: Pancho Villa and Ambrose Bierce, circa 1975
      - Two corrected typescript photocopies (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Two typescript photocopies—one inscribed, one annotated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Pancho Villa Projects: Ambrose Bierce and Pancho Villa, circa 1975
      - Typescript photocopy (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Pancho Villa Projects: Tom Mix and Pancho Villa, 1988-1989, undated
      - Research, notes, outlines (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Research, notes, outline printout (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Notes, correspondence, outline photocopy (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 7)